<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<odoo>
    <record id="demo_data_agreement" model="agreement">
        <field name="is_template">True</field>
        <field name="name">Demo Agreement</field>
        <field name="description">Demo Agreement</field>
        <field name="agreement_type_id" ref="agreement_legal.agreement_type_contract" />
        <field name="create_template">
        <![CDATA[
                    <div class="page" style="font-size:111%;">
                        <div class="col-12" style="text-align:center;">
                            <h3>CONSULTANCY SERVICE AGREEMENT</h3>
                        </div>
                        <br/><br/>
                        <div class="col-12" >
                            <p>
                                <b>THIS SERVICES AGREEMENT</b> _________________________________ is entered into this _________________________________, by and between
                                the _____________________________________having its principal
                                place of business at at 502, 5th floor, I-Square Corporate Park, Near CIMS Hospital, Science City Road, Ahmedabad - 380060
                                and ___________________________________having its principal place of business at 
                                ___________________________________________.
                            </p>
                        </div>
                            <br/>
                            <br/>
                        <div class="row">
                            <div class="col-1" style="text-align:left;"><b>1.</b></div>
                            <div class="col-11"><b>Definitions:</b></div>
                        </div>
                        <br/>
                        <div class="row">
                            <div class="col-1"><span></span></div>
                            <div class="col-1" style="text-align:left;"><span>i.</span></div>
                            <div class="col-8"><p><b>Incubator:</b> Business incubator is an organization that 
                            helps start-up companies and individual entrepreneurs to develop their 
                            businesses by providing a full-scale range of services starting with management 
                            training and office space and ending with venture capital financing.</p></div>
                        </div>
                        <div class="row">
                            <div class="col-1"><span></span></div>
                            <div class="col-1" style="text-align:left;"><span>ii.</span></div>
                            <div class="col-8"><p><b>Service Provider:</b> The person who is giving specified service 
                            in this agreement in exchange for a payment.</p></div>
                        </div>
                        <div class="row">
                            <div class="col-1"><span></span></div>
                            <div class="col-1" style="text-align:left;"><span>i.</span></div>
                            <div class="col-8"><p><b>Service Receiver::</b>  Service receiver is a person who receives 
                            or avails the service provided by the service provider.</p></div>
                        </div>  
                        <br/><br/>
                        <div class="col-12" >
                            <p>
                                <b>WHEREAS,</b> the service provider is ready and willing to 
                                provide this consultancy services for the purpose of assisting
                                the service receiver to avail such financial assistance.
                            </p>
                        </div>
                        <br/><br/>
                        <div class="row">
                            <div class="col-1" style="text-align:left;"><span>2.</span></div>
                            <div class="col-11"><p>
                                <b>WHEREAS,</b> service provider will be providing all the necessary 
                                information and guidance for the purpose of making an application to 
                                the incubators (nodal institution).
                            </p></div>
                        </div>
                        <br/>
                        <div class="row">
                            <div class="col-1" style="text-align:left;"><span>3.</span></div>
                            <div class="col-11"><p>
                                <b>WHEREAS,</b> service provider will be providing necessary 
                                guidance and advice to the service receiver to appear before
                                 Jury Committee at the time of reviewing of profile of the service receiver. 
                            </p></div>
                        </div>
                        <br/>
                        <div class="row">
                            <div class="col-1" style="text-align:left;"><span>4.</span></div>
                            <div class="col-11"><p>
                                <b>WHEREAS,</b> the service provider will also provide necessary 
                                advice and guidance while negotiating with the incubator.

                            </p></div>
                        </div>
                        <br/>
                        <div class="row">
                            <div class="col-1" style="text-align:left;"><span>5.</span></div>
                            <div class="col-11"><p>
                                <b>WHEREAS,</b> the service provider will also provide necessary 
                                guidance for the purpose of monitoring and reporting of performance 
                                of the service receiver to the incubator.
                            </p></div>
                        </div>
                        <br/><br/>
                        <div class="row">
                            <div class="col-1" style="text-align:left;"><b>6.</b></div>
                            <div class="col-11"><b>Covenants of Service Receiver:</b></div>
                        </div>
                        <div class="row">
                            <div class="col-1"><span></span></div>
                            <div class="col-1" style="text-align:left;"><span>i.</span></div>
                            <div class="col-8"><p><b>WHEREAS, </b> the service receiver acknowledges 
                            that, the amount paid to the service provider is non-refundable.</p></div>
                        </div>
                        <div class="row">
                            <div class="col-1"><span></span></div>
                            <div class="col-1" style="text-align:left;"><span>ii.</span></div>
                            <div class="col-8"><p><b>WHEREAS, </b>the service receiver shall pay 
                            an amount of <b>Rs. _________/- + GST INR</b> as consultancy fees to the service 
                            provider as follows:</p>
                            <span><b>First Stage:</b> ___% of the amount at the time of signing and executing the agreement.</span>
                            <span><b>Second Stage:</b>   Remaining ___% of the amount after approval of application.</span></div>
                        </div>
                        <br/><br/>
                        <div class="row">
                            <div class="col-1" style="text-align:left;"><b>7.</b></div>
                            <div class="col-11"><b>Covenants of Service Provider:</b></div>
                        </div>
                        <div class="row">
                            <div class="col-1"><span></span></div>
                            <div class="col-1" style="text-align:left;"><span>i.</span></div>
                            <div class="col-8"><p><b>WHEREAS,</b> the service provider assures and 
                            is obliged to maintain secrecy of the information/documents provided by
                            the service receiver and undertakes under no circumstances, the said
                            information will not be released to anyone except to the service receiver
                            or its authorized representative. </p></div>
                        </div>
                        <div class="row">
                            <div class="col-1"><span></span></div>
                            <div class="col-1" style="text-align:left;"><span>ii.</span></div>
                            <div class="col-8"><p><b>WHEREAS, </b> the Service Provider will be preparing all the documents 
                            that are required for the purpose of filing an application. On receipt of required 
                            data and details from the Service receiver and after preparing required 
                            reports and documents, Service Provider will submit the application on 
                            behalf of the Service Receiver. </p></div>
                        </div>
                        <br/><br/>
                        <div class="row">
                            <div class="col-1" style="text-align:left;"><span>8.</span></div>
                            <div class="col-11"><p>
                                <b>Term:</b>This agreement shall be valid, effective, and binding on both the Parties 
                                for a tenure of 1 (One) year commencing from the date of execution.
                            </p></div>
                        </div>
                        <br/><br/>
                        <div class="row">
                            <div class="col-1" style="text-align:left;"><span>9.</span></div>
                            <div class="col-11"><p>
                                <b>Termination:</b>Either party may terminate this Agreement at any 
                                time by giving prior written notice of not less than thirty (30) days 
                                to the other party by assigning the reason for the termination. 
                                Termination under any of the provisions of this Agreement shall 
                                be without prejudice to the service provider’s right to get paid 
                                by the service receiver for the service rendered till the date of Termination.

                            </p></div>
                        </div>
                        <br/><br/>
                        <div class="row">
                            <div class="col-1" style="text-align:left;"><span>10.</span></div>
                            <div class="col-11"><p>
                                <b>Relationship:</b>Each Party hereto is an independent contractor, 
                                responsible for its own actions. Nothing in this Agreement shall be
                                deemed to constitute or form an employment relationship, partnership, 
                                agency or other form of business relationship. Neither party shall have 
                                the right or authority to create any obligation, whether express or implied, 
                                on behalf of the other.

                            </p></div>
                        </div>
                        <br/><br/>
                        <div class="row">
                            <div class="col-1" style="text-align:left;"><span>11.</span></div>
                            <div class="col-11"><p>
                                <b>Third Parties:</b> This Agreement does not and shall not be 
                                deemed to confer upon any third party any right to claim damages 
                                to bring suit, or other proceeding against either the service 
                                receiver or service provider because of any term contained in this Agreement.

                            </p></div>
                        </div>
                        <br/><br/>
                        <div class="row">
                            <div class="col-1" style="text-align:left;"><span>12.</span></div>
                            <div class="col-11"><p>
                                <b>Entire Agreement:</b>This Agreement constitutes the entire 
                                agreement and understanding between the parties and supersedes 
                                any prior agreement or understanding relating to the subject 
                                matter of this Agreement.

                            </p></div>
                        </div>
                        <br/><br/>
                        <div class="row">
                            <div class="col-1" style="text-align:left;"><span>13.</span></div>
                            <div class="col-11"><p>
                                <b>Modification:</b>This Agreement may be modified or amended only 
                                by a duly authorized written instrument executed by the parties 
                                hereto by way of mutual understanding.

                            </p></div>
                        </div>
                        <br/><br/>
                        <div class="row">
                            <div class="col-1" style="text-align:left;"><span>14.</span></div>
                            <div class="col-11"><p>
                                <b>Severability:</b>If any of the provisions of this Agreement 
                                shall be invalid or unenforceable, such invalidity or unenforceability 
                                shall not invalidate or render unenforceable the entire Agreement, 
                                but rather the entire Agreement shall be construed as if not containing 
                                the particular invalid or unenforceable provision or provisions, and the 
                                rights and obligations of the party shall be construed and enforced 
                                accordingly, to effectuate the essential intent and purposes of this Agreement.

                            </p></div>
                        </div>
                        <br/><br/>
                        <div class="row">
                            <div class="col-1" style="text-align:left;"><span>15.</span></div>
                            <div class="col-11"><p>
                                <b>Enforcement and Waiver:</b> The failure of either party in any 
                                one or more instances to insist upon strict performance of any of 
                                the terms and provisions of this Agreement, shall not be construed 
                                as a waiver of the right to assert any such terms and provisions on 
                                any future occasion or of damages caused thereby.
                            </p></div>
                        </div>
                        <br/><br/>
                        <div class="row">
                            <div class="col-1" style="text-align:left;"><span>16.</span></div>
                            <div class="col-11"><p>
                                <b>Effective Date:</b>The effective date of this Agreement shall be 
                                the date first written above regardless of the date when the Agreement 
                                is actually signed or executed by both the parties.
                            </p></div>
                        </div>
                        <br/><br/>
                        <div class="row">
                            <div class="col-1" style="text-align:left;"><span>17.</span></div>
                            <div class="col-11"><p>
                                <b>Governing Law:</b>This Agreement shall be governed, in all respects 
                                in accordance with the laws of India and subject to the jurisdiction of 
                                Courts in Ahmedabad.

                            </p></div>
                        </div>
                        <br/><br/>
                        <div class="row">
                            <div class="col-1" style="text-align:left;"><span>18.</span></div>
                            <div class="col-11"><p>
                                <b>Notices:</b> Any and all notices, demands, or other communications 
                                required or desired to be given hereunder by any party hereto shall be 
                                in writing and shall be validly given or made to another party if 
                                personally served or if sent by Registered A/D. Post or by facsimile 
                                at the address mentioned herein or the last known address of the 
                                Recipient party. Any party hereto may change its address by a written 
                                notice given in the manner provided above.
                            </p></div>
                        </div>
                        <br/><br/>
                        <div class="row">
                            <div class="col-1" style="text-align:left;"><span>19.</span></div>
                            <div class="col-11"><p>
                                <b>Arbitration: </b> All disputes, differences and/or claims arising 
                                out of this agreement shall be first settled amicably by the parties 
                                inter-se. On failure of an amicable settlement, either Party may refer 
                                the dispute arising out of the terms of this agreement to arbitration 
                                in accordance with the provision contained in the Arbitration and 
                                Conciliation Act, 1996, and rules and regulations framed there under. 
                                The Parties, once the arbitration is invoked by way of Notice, 
                                appoint a mutually agreeable sole Arbitrator as per law. If the 
                                parties fail to come to an agreement for appointment of an arbitrator, 
                                the parties shall take a recourse for the appointment of arbitrator 
                                under Arbitration and Conciliation Act, 1996. The orders and award 
                                passed by the Arbitrator shall be final and binding on all the parties 
                                concerned. The arbitration proceedings shall be conducted in English 
                                and the venue of the Arbitration shall be at Ahmedabad, Gujarat.
                            </p></div>
                        </div>
                        <br/><br/>
                        <div class="row">
                            <div class="col-1" style="text-align:left;"><span>20.</span></div>
                            <div class="col-11"><p>
                                <b>Counterpart:</b> This Agreement may be executed in one or more 
                                counterparts, each of which will be deemed an original by which 
                                together will constitute one and the same instrument.
                            </p></div>
                        </div>
                        <br/><br/>
                        <div class="col-12" >
                            <p>
                                <b>IN WITNESS WHEREOF,</b>the parties have caused their duly authorized 
                                representatives to sign this<b>SERVICES AGREEMENT</b>as of the date first written above.
                            </p>
                        </div>
                        <br/><br/>
                        <table class="table table-sm table-bordered" style="border-color:black;">
                            <thead>
                                <tr>
                                    <th style="width:50%;height:100px;text-align:left;" ><p>Signed and delivered for and on behalf of</p></th>
                                    <th style="width:50%;height:100px;text-align:left;" ><p>I have read and understood the provisions of this Agreement and hereby accept the same.</p></th>
                                </tr>
                                <tr>
                                    <th style="width:50%;height:100px;text-align:left;" ><b>Name:</b>_</th>
                                    <th style="width:50%;height:100px;text-align:left;" ><b>Name:</b></th>
                                </tr>
                                <tr>
                                    <th style="width:50%;height:100px;text-align:left;" ><b>Title:</b></th>
                                    <th style="width:50%;height:100px;text-align:left;" ><b>Title:</b></th>
                                </tr>
                                <tr>
                                    <th style="width:50%;height:100px;text-align:left;" >Date:</th>
                                    <th style="width:50%;height:100px;text-align:left;" >Date:</th>
                                </tr>
                                <tr>
                                    <th style="width:50%;height:100px;text-align:left;" >Signature:</th>
                                    <th style="width:50%;height:100px;text-align:left;" >Signature:</th>
                                </tr>
                            </thead>
                        </table>
                    </div>
        ]]>
        </field>
    </record>
</odoo>